José Martín Govea López

Software Developer

+52 8341544686

Ciudad Victoria, Tamaulipas, México

https://martingovea.netlify.app/

in http://www.linkedin.com/in/magovz



I am an IT Engineer with 5+ years of experience working with technologies like HTML, CSS, SASS, Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS, JavaScript, React, Angular, Python, PHP, SQL. I really enjoy what I do and I am looking for a job opportunity where I can contribute with my knowledge and grow personally and professionally.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Software Developer, Vive Metria

Design and development of web pages.

- Development and maintenance of web applications (Laravel).
- Obtaining requirements.
- Database administration (SQL).

Software Developer, HTA

- Creation and development of designs (Front-End development).
- Development and maintenance of web applications (Django).
- Database administration (SQL).

Software Developer, DMAC

- Design and development of web pages.
- Development and maintenance of web applications (Laravel).
- Database administration (SQL).

Software Developer, Budget Planning Department of Tamaulipas (professional practices)

• Design and development of user interfaces for web and desktop applications.

09/2017 - 06/2018

04/2020 - 12/2022

Tamaulipas, México

06/2018 - 09/2019

Tamaulipas, México

Ciudad Victoria,

Ciudad Victoria,

Ciudad Victoria, Tamaulipas, México

11/2015 – 12/2015 Ciudad Victoria, Tamaulipas, México

SKILLS

Knowledge of HTML, CSS, SASS, JavaScript, jQuery, Node.js, Gulp.js.

PHP, Python, C#.

Experience with frameworks and development libraries (Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS, React, Angular, Django).

SQL.

LANGUAGES

Spanish (Native) • **English** (Intermediate)

EDUCATION

Information Technology Engineer, Universidad Politécnica de Victoria

09/2014 – 12/2017 Ciudad Victoria, Tamaulipas, México